bolegaindia.com 2010-11-21

# BolegaIndia.com - Connect with Friends, Ask Sawaal, Share Knowledge, Share Offers, Polls Predict & Win

Date of Last Revision: January 10th, 2010 

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you of BolegaIndia's policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any Personal Information you submit to us through our Sites. 

BolegaIndia ("BolegaIndia", "us" or "we") respects the privacy of the visitors to its Sites. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meanings assigned to such terms in the BolegaIndia Terms of Service and which incorporate this Privacy Policy by reference. 

"Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing. 

"Anonymous Information" means information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information; Anonymous Information does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect and use Personal Information and Anonymous Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Member Consent

By submitting Personal Information through our Sites, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. Your Personal Information may be processed by BolegaIndia in the country where it was collected. 

Personal Information

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our Sites. When you sign up for BolegaIndia Member account, you provide us with your name, email, gender, and birth date. During the registration process we give you the opportunity to provide additional profile information, such as your hometown, describing yourself, what are you really good at, your hobbies, and to add a picture of yourself, to help your friends connect with you. In some cases we may ask for additional information for security reasons or to provide specific services to you. Once you register you can visit your profile at any time to add or remove personal information about yourself. You can also add other information about yourself including your qualification, occupation, as well as your contact information. If such additional functionalities and features are provided to us by any of our partners (such as, but not limited to, media players for content provided by our licensors) the additional terms that govern your use of such functionalities and features are not incorporated into this Agreement, but shall govern your use of such functionalities and features and you hereby agree to comply with and be bound by such terms as a condition to your access and use of such functionalities and features. 

We may collect your telephone/mobile number and send you messages if you decide that you want to receive SMS, MMS, or other text messages from the Services. When you save other Personal Information in your profile we will collect any such information you enter. When you enter Personal Information throughout BolegaIndia using one of the features of the BolegaIndia, for example sawaals, offers, polls, predict & wins, comments, we will collect any such information you enter ("Publicly Posted Information"). When you contact us by sending us an email, we will collect your email addresses and any information contained in the email you send us. 

Once you register with BolegaIndia and sign in to our Services, you are not anonymous to us. We keep track of all the actions you take on BolegaIndia, such as adding a friend, posting a sawaal, viewing offers, participating in polls, participating in predict & win polls, indicating you “like” a post. In some cases you are also taking an action when you provide information or content to us. For example, if you share a photo, in addition to storing the actual content you uploaded, we might log the fact you shared it. If you are browsing the Sites without registering with BolegaIndia, you are anonymous to us, but we will collect the information listed below under Personal Information Collected via Technology. If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our Sites, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email inviting him or her to visit the Sites. BolegaIndia stores this information to send these invitations, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [help@bolegaindia.com](mailto:help@bolegaindia.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

Use of Personal Information & Content

Any visitor of the Sites can view your profile information and photos that you have uploaded to the BolegaIndia Community. You can control what part of your profile information and photos is visible to visitors of the Sites and which network of BolegaIndia members can see what information. 

To provide you with some of the features that the BolegaIndia Community offers to its members, we may use Personal Information that is stored in your profile after you have requested such features, for example to send invitation emails to people that you specified as being interested in joining the BolegaIndia Community. In order to provide useful information about social networks to people who might be interested in joining the BolegaIndia community, we may use your profile information and photos on the Sites to BolegaIndia members or when we send general newsletters to members of the BolegaIndia community. When you decide to view a Member's profile, we may show that BolegaIndia Member that you chose to view their profile. When you provide us with your telephone number, we may use the telephone number to send you the communications that you have requested to receive. If you decide to use certain features of the BolegaIndia (like sawaals, offers, polls, predict & wins, comments, and the like), some of th e Personal Information you entered into your BolegaIndia profile and any information, including Personal Information, that you enter using one of these features, might be used and displayed. 

BolegaIndia Members can use the search feature to search for other members by different criteria, like first name, last name, location or gender. The Personal Information that BolegaIndia Members enter into the BolegaIndia profile will be used for these searches. Please note that if you choose to show your location, as provided by you, the information that is provided to the Services about your location will be used within your Member profile and can be viewed and searched by other Members and visitors of the Sites. Please be aware that any information that is publicly posted throughout the BolegaIndia Community can be accessed by every visitor of the Sites. BolegaIndia may analyze any collected information for its own internal purposes. In addition, BolegaIndia may remove personally identifying information from collected information to render it anonymous. BolegaIndia may use Anonymous Information for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Information in its discretion. 

We use the information we collect to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience. Here are some more details on how we do that: 

| (a) | We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. We use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities, and to enforce our terms of service. For example, we ask for your date of birth to verify that you are over age 18 and so that we can better limit your access to content and advertisements that are not age appropriate.  
---|---  
   
(b) | We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. You may opt out of all communications except essential updates on your account notifications page. We may include content you see on BolegaIndia in the emails we send to you.  
   
(c) | To serve personalized advertising to you. We don’t share your information with advertisers without your consent. We allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements and we may use any of the non-personally identifiable attributes we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. For example, we might use your interest in cricket to show you ads for cricket equipment, but we do not tell the cricket equipment company who you are. You can see the criteria advertisers may select by visiting our advertising page. Even though we do not share your information with advertisers without your consent, when you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement there is a possibility that the advertiser may place a cookie in your browser and note that it meets the criteria they select  
   
(d) | Certain downloadable software applications and applets that we offer, such as photo uploaders, transmit data to us. We may not make a formal disclosure if we believe our collection of and use of the information is the obvious purpose of the application, such as the fact that we receive photos when you use our photo uploader. If we believe it is not obvious that we are collecting or using such information, we will make a disclosure to you the first time you provide the information to us so that you can decide whether you want to use that feature.  
   
(e) | If we are notified that a user is deceased, we may memorialize the user’s account. In such cases we restrict profile access to confirmed friends, and allow friends and family to write on the user’s Screen in remembrance. We may close an account if we receive a formal request from the user’s next of kin or other proper legal request to do so.  
  
Friend Information

We offer contact importer tools to help you upload your friends’ addresses so that you can find your friends on BolegaIndia, and invite your contacts who do not have BolegaIndia account to join. We use your profile information, the addresses you import through our contact importer, and other relevant information, to help you connect with your friends, including making suggestions to you and other users that you connect with on BolegaIndia. If you give us your password to retrieve those contacts, we will not store your password after you have uploaded your contacts’ information. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure

One of the primary reasons people use BolegaIndia is to share content with others. Examples include when you update your status, upload a photo, upload video, share a link, make a comment, write something on someone’s screen, or send someone a message. BolegaIndia does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy. 

We provide your Personal Information to third party service providers who work on behalf of or with BolegaIndia under confidentiality agreements to provide some of the services and features of the BolegaIndia Community and to help us communicate with BolegaIndia Members. These service providers may use your personal information to communicate with you about offers and services from BolegaIndia and our marketing partners. However, these service providers do not have any independent right to share this information. 

If you decide to use one of the additional services that are offered by our partners, we may forward Personal Information to these partners to enable them to provide the services that you requested. We also provide information to third-party advertising companies, as described in the next section. Please be aware that the handling of your Personal Information by our partners or the third-party advertising companies is governed by their privacy policy, not ours. 

We will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information, if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of BolegaIndia's Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by applicable law.   
If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

While providing you with privacy settings that you can use to restrict other users from accessing your information. We share your information with third parties when we believe the sharing is permitted by you, reasonably necessary to offer our services, or when is legally required to do so. Here are some more details on how we share your information: 

(a) | To help your friends find you. By default, we make certain information you have posted to your profile available in search results on BolegaIndia to help your friends find you.  
---|---  
   
(b) | When you make a payment on BolegaIndia. When you enter into transactions with others or make payments on BolegaIndia, we will only share transaction information with those third parties necessary to complete the transaction and will require those third parties to agree to respect the privacy of your information.  
   
(c) | When you ask us to invite a friend to join BolegaIndia, we will send your friend a message on your behalf using your name. We may also send up to two reminders to them in your name. If your friend does not want us to keep their information, we will remove it at their request.  
   
(d) | When you choose to share your information with marketers. You may choose to share information with marketers or electronic commerce providers that are not associated with BolegaIndia through on-site offers. This is entirely at your discretion and we will not provide your information to these marketers without your consent.  
   
(e) | To give search engines access to publicly available information. We generally limit search engines’ access to our site. We may allow them to access information set to the “everyone” setting.  
   
(f) | We may ask advertisers outside of BolegaIndia to display ads promoting our services. We may ask them to deliver those ads based on the presence of a cookie, but in doing so will not share any other information with the advertiser.  
   
(g) | We may provide information to service providers that help us bring you the services we offer. For example, we may use third parties to help host our website, send out email updates about BolegaIndia, remove repetitive information from our user lists, process payments, or provide search results or links (including sponsored links). These service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service.  
   
(h) | To respond to legal requests and prevent harm. We may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters) if we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law. This may include respecting requests from jurisdictions outside of India where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our Terms of Service. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts or other government entities.  
  
Third Party Advertising

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our Sites. These companies may use Personal Information, such as gender or age, and other information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Sites and other webSites, such as time of day of the login, IP address or information about the internet service provider (ISP) or mobile device Carrier, in order to provide advertisements on the Sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here. 

Personal Information Collected Via Technology

When you access BolegaIndia from a computer, mobile phone, or other device, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our server logs, including your Internet protocol (IP) address, location, browser type, operating system, as well as the pages you visit. If you send SMS, MMS, or text messages to the Services, we will collect the telephone number (if any) from which such communication was sent. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Sites you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our Services and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the BolegaIndia Community experience to meet your special interests and needs. If you search the BolegaIndia Community by using a toolbar that BolegaIndia, or a third party provides, we may collect Anonymous Information about you automatically, but we will not collect Personal Information. 

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. In some cases your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer internet access provider, your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We track your IP Address when you login to the Sites. 

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a web Site sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web Sites. We use "Cookies" to make BolegaIndia easier to use, to make our advertising better, and to protect both you and BolegaIndia. For example, we use them to store your login ID (but never your password) to make it easier for you to login whenever you come back to BolegaIndia. We also use them to confirm that you are logged into BolegaIndia, and to know when you are interacting with the Sites. BolegaIndia may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on the Sites. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following your Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Sites may not work properly. Other third parties may place advertisements and cookies on webpages within the BolegaIndia Community. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Profile, Account Information and Preferences

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the BolegaIndia Newsletter, that are considered part of your BolegaIndia account. If you would like to opt out of certain messages, log into BolegaIndia and go to your account settings by clicking the account link. On that page you can edit your preferences. You may change or delete your profile information at any time by going to your profile page and clicking “edit” Information will be updated immediately. While you cannot delete your date of birth, you can use the privacy setting to hide all or part of it from other members. If you want to stop using your account you may delete it. If you would like to delete your account, log into BolegaIndia, go to your settings page by clicking the settings link. On that page, you will be provided with the Delete Account option to delete your account. There are limitations on removal of content. Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users. Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies with us for up to 90 days, but will not be available to others. 

If a user provides your email address to us, and you are not a BolegaIndia member and you want us to delete your address, you can do so by emailing us at [support@bolegaindia.com.](mailto:support@bolegaindia.com) However, that request will only apply to addresses we have at the time of the request and not to any addresses that users provide to us later. 

Confidentiality and Security 

We take steps to ensure that others use information that you share on BolegaIndia in a consistent manner with your privacy settings, but we cannot guarantee that they will follow our rules. We designed our privacy settings to enable you to control how you share your personal information on BolegaIndia. You should review the default privacy settings to make sure they reflect your preferences. Here are some specific things to remember:  (a) | You can control the visibility of most of the information you share on BolegaIndia through the privacy settings you select.  
---|---  
   
(b) | Certain categories of personal information such as your name, profile photo, list of friends, gender, geographic location, and networks you belong to are considered publicly available, and therefore do not have privacy settings. You can limit the ability of others to find this information.  
   
(c) | Some of the content you share and the actions you take will show up on your friends’ home pages and other pages they visit.  
   
(d) | Even after you remove information from your profile or delete your account, copies of that information may remain viewable elsewhere to the extent it has been shared with others, it was otherwise distributed pursuant to your privacy settings, or it was copied or stored by other users.  
   
(e) | You understand that information might be re-shared or copied by other users.  
   
(f) | Certain types of communications that you send to other users cannot be removed, such as messages.  
   
(g) | When you post information on another user’s profile or comment on another user’s post, that information will be subject to the other user’s privacy settings.  
   
(h) | When you post information on another user’s profile or comment on another user’s post, that information will be subject to the other user’s privacy settings.  
  
Information set to “everyone” is publicly available information, may be accessed by everyone on the Internet (including people not logged into BolegaIndia), is subject to indexing by third party search engines, may be associated with you outside of BolegaIndia (such as when you visit other sites on the internet), and may be imported and exported by us and others without privacy limitations. The default privacy setting for certain types of information you post on BolegaIndia is set to “everyone.” You can review and change the default settings in your privacy settings. If you delete “everyone” content that you posted on BolegaIndia, we will remove it from your BolegaIndia profile, but have no control over its use outside of BolegaIndia. 

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and third parties who we reasonably believe need access to that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you and your BolegaIndia account information is protected by a password that you select. BolegaIndia uses industry-standard SSL encryption in certain areas of the Sites to protect data transmissions. However, no company, including BolegaIndia, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

We keep your account information on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers and passwords), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We also use automated and social measures to enhance security, such as analyzing account behavior for fraudulent or otherwise anomalous behavior, may limit use of site features in response to possible signs of abuse, may remove inappropriate content or links to illegal content, and may suspend or disable accounts for violations of our Terms of Service. 

Although we allow you to set privacy options that limit access to your information, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other members with whom you share your information. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We cannot ensure that information you share on BolegaIndia will not become publicly available. We are not responsible for third party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures on BolegaIndia. You can reduce these risks by using common sense security practices such as choosing a strong password, using different passwords for different services, and using up to date antivirus software. 

Exporting Personal Information

You (and those you make your information available to) may use tools like RSS feeds, mobile phone address books, or copy and paste functions, to capture and export information from BolegaIndia, including your personal information and additional information about you. 

Information from other Websites

When you click on links on BolegaIndia, you may leave our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, and we encourage you to read their privacy statements. Our provision of a link to any other Sites or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other Sites or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside Sites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy does not apply to these outside BolegaIndia. 

We may from time to time institute programs with advertising partners and other websites in which they share information with us. We may ask advertisers to tell us how our users responded to the ads we showed them (and for comparison purposes, how other users who didn’t see the ads acted on their site). This data sharing, commonly known as “conversion tracking,” helps us measure our advertising effectiveness and improve the quality of the advertisements you see. We may receive information about whether or not you’ve seen or interacted with certain ads on other sites in order to measure the effectiveness of those ads. If in any of these cases we receive data that we do not already have, we will stop associating the information with any particular user within ninety "90 days". 

Regarding Children

We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 18. If you are under age 18, please do not attempt to register on BolegaIndia or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 18, please contact us through this help page. 

Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

BolegaIndia.com Web Pvt. Ltd.   
Attn: Privacy Department  
C-1, IGM Tower,  
Gopinath Marg, New Colony,  
M.I.Road, Jaipur-302001 | Rajasthan - India   

Consent to Collection and Processing in India

By using BolegaIndia, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in India. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy

BolegaIndia may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat Personal Information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your BolegaIndia account or by placing a prominent notice on our Sites. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our Sites. Continued use of our Sites following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.
